# Kip Taylor



### PROFILE

After running my own business for two years, I returned to school and decided to complete a degree in Computer Science. I am a motivated self-learner and very excited to learn new technologies to apply in the business and consumer sector.

### CONTACT



(614) 795 8200



Kip.taylor123@gmail.com



LinkedIn

#### EDUCATION

# **Kent State University BS Computer Science**

Expected Graduation May 2022 Major GPA: 3.15

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Co-Founder / Transmount Leather Bag Company Jan 2018- Dec 2019

- Opened and ran a full-time luxury leather bag company.
  Involving international sales, deals and securing product routes.
- Responsible for all website content along with advertisement and company financials.

# Associate / Jet's Pizza Dec 2014 – Jul 2015

- Crafter and improved customer relations
- Handled complaints and request of customers
- Tasked with additional responsibilities when understaffed
- Strived to provide the best food and service bar none

## Associate / Papa Johns Jun 2014- Nov 2014

- Created and insured quality of customer orders
- Resolved customer complaints and provided a quality experience
- Tasked with additional responsibilities with opening and closing

#### SKILLS AND EXTRA CURRICLARS

- C++
- Docker
- React
- HTML/CSS/JSX
- Boy Scouts and Cub Scouts 12 years
- Founded a tutoring group via Discord to assist fellow CS students.